Guide to the Ipas Records, 1965-2020; 1965-ongoing RL.00617
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Program Files and Internal Documentation, 1970-2011; 32 boxes
  - External Conferences attended by Ipas staff and Ipas-sponsored conferences for external audiences: International Confederation of Midwives 23rd International Congress, Vancouver, Canada, May 9-14, 1993; UNFPA African Forum on Adolescent Reproductive Health, Addis Ababa, Ethiopia, January 1997; Linking Research to Action: Innovative Approaches to Improve Adolescent Sexual and Reproductive Health in Africa, Accra, Ghana, October 2-6, 2000; Making Abortion Safe & Accessible, Bhubeaneswar, India, October 15-17,2001; International Conference on Law, Reproductive Health and Human Rights, Abuja, Nigeria, August 19-22, 2003; African Women's Sexual and Reproductive Health and Rights Conference, Johannesburg, South Africa, February 4-7, 2003; 2nd Annual RHINO Workshop on Enhancing the Quality and Use of Routine Health Information at District Level, Eastern Cape, South Africa, September 29-October 4,2003; Countdown 2015: ICPD at 10, Global Roundtable, London, UK, August 30 – September 2, 2004; From Controversy to Consensus on Abortion, Abortion Working Group, London, UK, August 31-September 21, 2004; Grantmakers without Borders 4th Annual Conference: global Policy, Grassroots Change, Miami Beach, FL, October 14-16, 2004; Strategies for Protecting Human Research Subjects Globally, Chapel Hill, NC, August 2-3, 2004; Medical Students for Choice New England Regional Conference: Choice in 2004: Exploring our Belief Systems, Hanover, NH, November 13, 2004; Women Coming Together: Claiming the Law for Social Change, Cincinnati, OH, February 2005; Reproductive Justice for All: A U.S. Policy Conference, Northampton, MA, November 10-15, 2005; Technical Meeting on Promoting Sexual and Reproductive Health and Reproductive Rights – Reducing Poverty and Achieving the MDGs, Stockholm, Sweden, October 5-6,2004; PPFA National Medical Conference, St. Petersburg, FL, September 9-11, 2005; Pre-Conference Workshop on SRHR – FLASOG, Santo Domingo, DR, May 14-15, 2005; Rights, Respect, Responsibility: A Bold New Vision for Sexual health in America, Eugene, OR, august 10-11, 2006; SURGE Conference, Raleigh, NC, February 24, 2006; EC in LAC Meeting, October 4, 2006; Mifepristone Medical Abortion: The Good, the Bad and the Challenging, NYC, NY, June 1-2, 2006 (Box 129)
  - External Conferences attended by Ipas staff and Ipas-sponsored conferences for external audiences: Women Deliver Global Conference, London, UK, October 18020, 2007; Women's Options Initiative: Family Planning Conference, Bronx, NY, September 19, 2007; ARMM Workshop, Brighton, UK, April 17-18, 2007; Utilizing the Strategic Approach to Reduce Unsafe Abortion and Strengthen Reproductive health Services: An Africa Regional Workshop; Nairobi, Kenya; April 17-20, 2007; Reproductive Health 101: Reporting on the "Un-covered" Story of the Latino Immigration, Chapel Hill, NC, Februrary 13, 2007; Global Safe Abortion Conference 2007, London, UK, October 23-24, 2007; The Partnership for Maternal, Newborn & Child Health: Partner's Forum Meeting, Dar Es Salaam, Tanzania, April 17-20, 2007; International Conference on Second Trimester Abortion, London, UK, March 29-31, 2007; 4th Asia Pacific Conference on Reproductive and Sexual Health and Rights: Exploring New Frontiers, Hyderabad, India, October 29-31, 2007; Sharing, Learning, Growing: Coalition Building Among Abortion Activists, London, UK, October 22, 2007; Seizing the Initiative in a New Political Climate: the 9th Annual Mifepristone Medical Abortion Meeting; NYC, NY, June 7, 2007; National Summit to Ensure The Health and Humanity of Pregnant and Birthing Women, Atlanta, GA, January 18-21, 2007; Community Health: International conference on Global Health, Washington, DC, May 27-31, 2008; 2008 Annual Meeting of Taiwan Association of Obstetrics and Gynecology, Taiwan, March 15-16, 2008; Reproductive Justice Training by SisterSong, Chapel Hill, NC, May 22, 2008; Royal College of OB/GYNs, 7th International Scientific Meeting, Montreal, Canada, September 17-20, 2008; Making the Most of It: Maximizing the Potential of Medical Abortion, the 10th Annual Mifepristone Medical Abortion Meeting, NYC, NY, June 2, 2008; Priority Setting for Systematic Reviews, Baltimore, MD, July 10-11, 2008; 3rd Africa Conference on Sexual Health and Rights: Sexuality, Poverty & and Accountability in Africa, Abuja, Nigeria, February 4-7, 2008 (Box 130)
  - U.S. Program Files: 1999-2007 Mid-level abortion providers 99; bibliography 99; programs/reports descriptions 99-02; MVA slide presentation 00; MVA collaboration mtg 00; program eval and monitoring 00-02; FAQs 01; trainers/questionnaires 01; presentations 01; consultants 01; trainings requested 01; newsletters 01-03; donor reports and proposals 01-03; planning and results 01-03; trip report 02; trainer questionnaire 02; planning 02; training needs assessment 02; mid-level providers paper 02; correspondence/planning 02; planning emails 02-03; Lincoln med and MH Center MVA training 03; IDEAS (data) 03; meetings for exhibits 03; MVA trainings 03; ARHP MVA education 03; NC research 04-05; T.A. lit review 05; think tank 05; U.S. national research 05; student papers on Latina issues 05; el Foro 06; Latino health coalition 06; NC advocacy work 06; gender or sex 06; NC network of immigrants 06; U.S. voices 06; NC Latina project 06; NC women united 06; training NC project 06; immigration NC project 06; U.S. map restrictions 06; NC pregnancy adolescent guide 06; strategies and priorities 06; national advocacy NILRH 06; NC justice center 06; workplans 06-07; pregnancy options brochure (Spanish) 06-07; NC prevention first campaign 07; NC consultant 07 (Box 146)
  - External Conferences attended by Ipas staff and Ipas sponsored-conferences for external audiences 1997-2010: FIGO 1997 General Programme; Alance Promocion para el Desarrollo y Juventud, A.C., Processo de Formacion de Jovenes Activistas en el Tema de Aborto Carpeta de Trabajo, Diciembre 2002 a Junio 2003; It's Not the Same: 2003 Political Academy & Congressional Day of Action, Organizing to Win: Reality Camp, Planned Parenthood Federation of America, Inc., July 15 – 17, 2003, Capitol Hill, Washington, DC; Seminario – Taller: Guia Tecnica y de Politicas para Sistemas de Salud OMS, Cochabamba, 9 al 11 de Marzo del 2005 – Hotel "DIPLOMAT"; Acting on Rights: The Women and HIV/AIDS Leadership Retreat 6-8 July 2005, Yale Law School; Reunion de Expertas sobre Alternativas de Atencion en el Sector Salud a Mujeres Sobrevivientos de Violencia Sexual, Organizado por la Unidad de Genero,Etnia y Salud Organizacion Panamericana de la Salud/Organizacion Munduial de la Salud y el IPAS, Con la colaboracion de: OMS, ASDI, NORAD y la Fundacion Ford, Washington, D.C., 2 al 4 de Agosto de 2005; Reunion Validacoin del modelo de leyes y politicas sobre violencia intrafamliar contra las mujeres Iniciativa de la Unidad Genergo, Etnia, y Salud de la Organizacion Panamericana de la Salud (OPS/OMS), la Comision Interamericana de Mujeres (CM/OEA), UNFPA, UNIFEM, CLADEM, IPAS, ISIS International, el Grupo Parlamentario Inernacional y el Centro de Derechos Reproductivos 6 al 8 de Septiembre de 2005, Washington, D.C.; Financial Management of NGO Implemented Outputs & Working Group on Preventing and Addressing Sexual Violence in Central America LACD/Spain Cooperation Fund for LAC UNFPA 22-23 April 2008; International Confederation of Midwives 28th Triennial Congress Glasgow 1 – 5, June 2008; AWID South Africa Sep 2008; "Respeto, Promocion y Garania del Derecho a la Salud. Monitoreando su cumplimiento." Managua, Nicaragua del 09 al 13 de Diciembre, 2008; The 53rd UN CSW Parallel Event: Local Policies and Gender Governance toward a Caring Society March 3, 2009; Curso International: Asegurando un suministro continuo de tecnologias apropiadas para la evacuacion endouterina: desarrollo de planes de suministro para Bolivia; Mexico, DF; y Peru, Hotel el Pueblo, Lima del 10 al 12 de Junio de 2009; SVRI Forum 2009 Conference Report: 6-9 July 09 Johannesburg, South Africa; Global Partners in Action: NGO Form on Sexual and Reproductive Health and Development, Berlin, Germany, September 2-4, 2009; Taller Regional de Coordinacion del Fondo de Cooperaction UNFPA/AECID para America Latina y el Caribe 2008-2011, 2-4 de junio de 2010; Programme XVIII International AIDS Conference 18-23 July Vienna Austria; Programme Supplement AIDS 2010 XVIII International AIDS Conference July 18-23, 2010, Vienna Austria (Box 185-186)
  - Ipas Internal Trainings and Workshops 02-10: Level One Leadership Training Series July 17-19, 2002; Program Mgt Initiative Rationale, WG Results Nov 03 – July 04; Africa Region PMI Workshop Facilitator's Manual November 23-25, 2004; Capacity Building Workshop for Lead Trainers and Implementers May 28 – June 1, 2007 Chang Mai, Thailand; Planning for a sustainable supply of manual vacuum aspiration instruments: Developing plans for selected states and regions of Nigeria and Ghana, Greenland Hotel, Agona Swedu, Ghana January 29 – February 1, 2008; Ipas Providers as Advocates for Safe Abortion Care Staff Workshop – April 29, 2008, The Stone House – Mebane, NC; CEM Global Meeting, Kathmandu, Nepal, November 10-13, 2009; Global Directors Meeting 1-4 February 2010 (Box 187)
  - RWD/CEM 07-11: GFW FY07; RWD Concept FY07; Strategic Plans 07-11; Nepal CEM activities 08; Concept paper FY08; CFW board 08; WGNRR FY08; RWD Report w/ICRW FY08; India MA work 08-09; RWD/CEM Materials & Reports FY08-FY10; Games for Change conf 09; Quarterly Updates 09; Presentation to ET 09; Hessini Papers/Presentation 09; Papers/Presentations 09; Women's Global Network for RR Amsterdam trip 09; WGNRR FY09; Sister Song FY09; WHO/Injectables 09; Rights/MA/Restrictive FY09; LAC Field Visit Reports FY09; Mexico Pharmacy Follow-Up 09; Unsafe Abortion in Arab World FY09; Zambia Proposal FY09; India FY09; Eval Background 09; Ipas IEC Materials FY09; Global Fund for Women 09; Ghana Planning 09-10; Donor Presentations 09-10; Donor Proposals/Reports FY09-10; Ma at the community level 09-11; Stigma workshop 10; MA at community level 6/10; Output 1 meeting 10; Sister Song 2009 board mtg FY10; 2010 Planning 2010; Policy Opposition Presentation 10; Men & Abortion FY10; Global Mtg Planning FY10; South Africa 10; Nepal 10; Overview of Unit 10; Nepal Radio program 10; Logframe FY10; Community Access in LAC mtg 10; Staff Retreat 10; Feminism in ME – Jordan mtg 10; RFP – Jharkhand MA 10; Toolkit FY10; Youth Work 2011 plans FY10; MA & Youth 2010; Trip Reports FY10; M+E 2010; NY Rain FY10; Stigma Background Materials 2010; Stigma Mtg 5/2010; Hessini Stigma Article FY2010; Stigma Presentation FY10; FY10 Results FY10; Young Women and Abortion FY10; Staff Tasks FY10; GFW 2010; Zambia Interviews FY10; Zambia Planning FY10, Unit Mtg FY10; Brownbag on CEM Mtg FY10; War & Sexual Violence FY10; Youth Strategy FY10; ICMA Conf Report 2010; Ipas Overview FY10; Uruguay 2010; Anon 2 New Proposal FY10; Donor Visit 2010; WEGS Consultancy 2011; MA at Community Level: Internal Discussions FY11; Ghana FY11; Indicators FY11; Presentations FY11; CEM Planning FY11; Ipas Directors FY11; M&E FY11; CEM Unit Mtgs FY11; Stigma FY11 (Box 188)
  - Youth 06-10: Latino NC 06-09; Brasil Workshop FY09; Youth Meeting Nigeria & Planning 09; SA Youth Center Eval 09; M&E mtg on LAC RWD & Youth 09; SA Study Tour 09; Background Materials 09; Zambia Background – Capacity Building Workshop FY10; Sexado Radio Program FY10; Youth Advocacy workshop Kenya FY10; Ipas Youth Strategy 10; Youth Stats FY10; MA & Youth 10; Staff Survey FY10; Workplan FY10 (Box 189)
  - External Conferences attended by Ipas staff and Ipas sponsored-conferences for external audiences: Vietnam Training of Trainers to Conduct Effective Training Courses, Hanoi, Vietnam, November 18-22, 2002; 10th Reproductive Health Priorities Conference, Johannesburg, South Africa, October 14-17, 2003; WHO 18th Meeting of the Policy and Coordination Committee (PCC), Geneva, Switzerland, June 30-July 1, 2005; 3rd international symposium on Misoprostol and Mifepristone in Obstetrics and Gynecology, Valencia, Spain, October 4-5, 2007; WHO 22nd Meeting of the Policy and Coordination Committee, Geneva, Switzerland, June 18-19, 2009; Women Deliver, Washington DC, June 2010; Partners Workshop: Action on Maternal Mortality in Africa Project May 27-28, 2010; Keeping Our Promise: Addressing Unsafe Abortion in Africa, Accra, Ghana, November 8-11, 2011; International Seminar on the Health, Economic and Social Consequences of Unsafe Abortion, San Juan del Rio, Mexico, November 10-12, 2010, 2002-2011 (Box 194)
  - Internal Ipas Workshops/Meetings: Strategic Planning FY12-16, Global Directors' Meeting, Chapel Hill, NC, February 1-4, 2010; CEM/Output 2 Global Meeting; Addis Ababa, Ethiopia, April 12-16, 2011; Making Safe Abortion a Reality; Participant Notebook; Chapel Hill, NC, May 16-20, 2011; Understanding Abortion Stigma, CEM Capacity Building; Chapel Hill, NC, may 25-27, 2010, 2010-2011 (Box 201)
  - Medical Abortion 92-07: T Baird MA paper 92; comms RU486 93; WHO MA mtg 94; SIDA MA proposal 05; Fiala paper 05; Gynuity mife mtg 06; clostridia 06; EC vs MA 06; PAC use 06; dosage 06; Methotrexate 06; Free Maternity Worldwide 06; AMREF 06; Gynuity PAC 06; ethics consultant SOW 06; tools development 06; materials/tools 06; WHO MA mtg 06; miso background 06-08; MA update 07; checklists/presentations 07; core team 07; resources 10; MA notebook 06-07 (Box 206)
  - External Conferences attended by Ipas staff and Ipas sponsored-conferences for external audiences: Dateline 2010, Global Health Goals & Metrics, Washington DC, June 14-18, 2010; Foro Regional: Articulando Agendas para la Reduccion del Aborto Inseguro en America Latina y el Caribe, Quito, Ecuador, September 16-17, 2010; EuroNGOs Conference, London, UK, November 9, 2010; Foro sobre el Aseguramiento de Insumos para la Salud Reproductiva, Panama City, Panama, July 20-22, 2011; Avances y Desafios en el Acceso a Salud y Justicia para Mujeres ante la Violencia Sexual en Centroamerica, San Salvador, El Salvador, September 20, 2011; Innovations in Abortion Care, New Orleans, LA, October 16-17, 2011; Funders Network on Population and Reproductive Health and Rights, Santa Cruz, CA, November 9-11, 2011; 10th Congreso Mudial de Medicina Perinatal, Punta del Este, Uruguay, November 8-11, 2011; 2011 International Conference on Family Planning, Dakar, Senegal, November 29-December 2, 2011. Internal Trainings and Workshops: Making Safe Abortion a Reality, Chapel Hill, NC, May 16-20, 2011; Capacity Building workshop, Chapel Hill, NC, September 12-17, 2011; Communication & Collaboration Skills, Chapel Hill, NC, September 26-27, 2011 and October 25-26, 2011; The Next Generation: Expanding Impact Worldwide through Innovative Programs, Structures and Systems, Chapel Hill, NC October 17-27, 2011; Ipas Non Traditional Donors: Ideation Workshop, Chapel Hill, NC, November 28-29, 2011; From RX to CX: Ipas Community Access Global Meeting, Chapel Hill, NC, May 2012. (Box 208)
  - External Conferences attended by Ipas staff and Ipas sponsored-conferences for external audiences: Dateline 2010, Global Health Goals & Metrics, Washington DC, June 14-18, 2010; Foro Regional: Articulando Agendas para la Reduccion del Aborto Inseguro en America Latina y el Caribe, Quito, Ecuador, September 16-17, 2010; EuroNGOs Conference, London, UK, November 9, 2010; Foro sobre el Aseguramiento de Insumos para la Salud Reproductiva, Panama City, Panama, July 20-22, 2011; Avances y Desafios en el Acceso a Salud y Justicia para Mujeres ante la Violencia Sexual en Centroamerica, San Salvador, El Salvador, September 20, 2011; Innovations in Abortion Care, New Orleans, LA, October 16-17, 2011; Funders Network on Population and Reproductive Health and Rights, Santa Cruz, CA, November 9-11, 2011; 10th Congreso Mudial de Medicina Perinatal, Punta del Este, Uruguay, November 8-11, 2011; 2011 International Conference on Family Planning, Dakar, Senegal, November 29-December 2, 2011. Internal Trainings and Workshops: Making Safe Abortion a Reality, Chapel Hill, NC, May 16-20, 2011; Capacity Building workshop, Chapel Hill, NC, September 12-17, 2011; Communication & Collaboration Skills, Chapel Hill, NC, September 26-27, 2011 and October 25-26, 2011; The Next Generation: Expanding Impact Worldwide through Innovative Programs, Structures and Systems, Chapel Hill, NC October 17-27, 2011; Ipas Non Traditional Donors: Ideation Workshop, Chapel Hill, NC, November 28-29, 2011; From RX to CX: Ipas Community Access Global Meeting, Chapel Hill, NC, May 2012. (Box 208)
  - Internal and External Conferences/Meetings: 2010-2012. External Conferences attended by Ipas staff and Ipas sponsored-conferences for external audiences: Dateline 2010, Global Health Goals & Metrics, Washington DC, June 14-18, 2010; Foro Regional: Articulando Agendas para la Reduccion del Aborto Inseguro en America Latina y el Caribe, Quito, Ecuador, September 16-17, 2010; EuroNGOs Conference, London, UK, November 9, 2010; Foro sobre el Aseguramiento de Insumos para la Salud Reproductiva, Panama City, Panama, July 20-22, 2011; Avances y Desafios en el Acceso a Salud y Justicia para Mujeres ante la Violencia Sexual en Centroamerica, San Salvador, El Salvador, September 20, 2011; Innovations in Abortion Care, New Orleans, LA, October 16-17, 2011; Funders Network on Population and Reproductive Health and Rights, Santa Cruz, CA, November 9-11, 2011; 10th Congreso Mudial de Medicina Perinatal, Punta del Este, Uruguay, November 8-11, 2011; 2011 International Conference on Family Planning, Dakar, Senegal, November 29-December 2, 2011. Internal Trainings and Workshops: Making Safe Abortion a Reality, Chapel Hill, NC, May 16-20, 2011; Capacity Building workshop, Chapel Hill, NC, September 12-17, 2011; Communication & Collaboration Skills, Chapel Hill, NC, September 26-27, 2011 and October 25-26, 2011; The Next Generation: Expanding Impact Worldwide through Innovative Programs, Structures and Systems, Chapel Hill, NC October 17-27, 2011; Ipas Non Traditional Donors: Ideation Workshop, Chapel Hill, NC, November 28-29, 2011; From RX to CX: Ipas Community Access Global Meeting, Chapel Hill, NC, May 2012. (Box 210)
  - VHS tapes of advocacy meeting with mid-level providers and IHCAR/Karolinska Institute, 2001 (Box 211)
  - Abortion Research Methodologies Conference, 1989. Tapes and transcripts (Box 212)
- Executive and Management Files, 1965-2014; 46 boxes
  - Board of Directors correspondence: Correspondence 1986-1996, Infection control correspondence, 1991-1993, Len Laufe 1989-1993, Don Collins 1988-2003, Rebecca Cook 1995-1998, Louise Tyrer 1990-1997, Pouru Bhiwandiwala 1989-2002, Don Minkler 1989-2001, Alta Charo 1992-1993, Jose Pinotti 1992-1994, Orientation 1993, Marcie Musser 1990-1993, Judy Senderowitz 1990-1994, Davy Chikamata 1988-1998, Aziza Husein 1989-1991, Grace Delano 1992-1993, Lance Bronnenkant 1992-2002, Anne Firth Murray 1994-2001, Nicki Nichols Gamble 1994-2001, Ellen Hardy 1997-2001, Dilys Cossey 1996-2004, Paul Blumenthal 1997-2004, Jane Bertrand 2000-2001, Mahmoud Fathalla 2000-02, Gordon Duncas 2000-2005, Jael Silliman 1995-1999, Mable Biano 2002, Angela Kumara 2002-2003, Abe Nkomo 2002-2003, Fred Nunes 2002 (Box 88)
  - OC repackaging 1965-1974, Paper pill project 1974-1975, Trademark 1974-1976, Dr. Paniker (Malaysia) 1974-1980, Patent 1975-1978, Estillita (Brazil) 1975-1978, Egypt husband pill 1976-1977, Malaysia 1976-1980, Fundraising 1977-1978, Wyeth 1978, Battelle report 1978-1979, Mexico clinics 1979-1981, Sales reports 1980-1982, Mexico University Clinic 1980-1982, APSAM 81, Ann Leonard Thai refugee camp research 1985, Ann Leonard correspondence 1986-1989, General info 1987-1988, By-laws and charter 1987-1993, Policies and resolutions 1988-1990, Duff Gillespie's declaration 1990, Plata correspondence 1990-1991, Contract Package 1990, IPAS Clinic Program Loan Application 1975 (Box 89)
  - FDA labeling 1991, PAFP talk 1991, Abortion in the developing world talk K. McLaurin 1991, Forrest Greenslade notes 1991, Strategic planning 1991-1994, F. Greenslade Europe trip 1992, Norplant meeting 1992, APHA 1992, PAFP working group 1992, Staff meetings 1992, John Dorward 1992-1993, Labeling 1992-1995, PAHO 1992-1996, CFC 1992-1996, F. Greenslades messages to Board 1992-1996, Priorities 1993, RHTP 1993, New Delhi presentation F. Greenslade 1993, RU 486 meeting 1993, World Health Organization medical abortion meeting 1993, Staff meetings 1993, Nice letters 1993, Ann Leonard correspondence and internal memos 1993, Katie McLaurin correspondence and internal memos, Personnel policy review 1993, Fundraising 1993, Internal Correspondence 1993, 20th anniversary 1993, Evaluations 1993, Organization overview 1993, "The Grid" 1993, Ann Leonard talks 1993, General presentations 1993, APLIC meeting 1993, USAID talk 1993, Executive office correspondence 1993-1994, Letters other staff 1993-1994, Internal memos 1993-1994, Other correspondence 1993-1994 (Box 90)
  - CAs meeting 1994, Europe trip 1994, PAFP talk Ann Leonard 1994, RHFP presentation K. McLaurin 1994, Ipas overview for IHCAR K. McLaurin 1994, Ann Leonard correspondence 1994, Senior staff meetings 1994, staff meetings 1994, K. McLaurin correspondence 1994, F. Greenslade correspondence 1994, JHPIEGO letter of understanding 1994, MVA statistics 1994, World Health Organization medical abortion meeting 1994, ICPD 1994, FIGO 1994, F. Greenslade Brazil trip 1994, Strategic planning 1994-1995, Introducing MA technologies 1995, Prep for Beijing 1995, Senior staff meetings 1995, Khama Rogo talk 1995, donor meeting 1995, A. Leonard correspondence 1995, F. Greenslade correspondence 1995 (Box 91)
  - IT 1996, F. Greenslade correspondence 1996, Technology transfer paper 1996, Senior staff meetings 1996, LOGIX Egypt 1996-1998, Pharmatec 1996-1999, Accomplishments 1997, Measuring Our Reach 1997, Strategic planning notebook 1998, IT capacity 1998, Quinacrine 1998, Dialapan 1998, Personnel policies 1998-2000, A. Leonard Correspondence 1998-2000, Liz Maguire correspondence 1999, Matrix materials 1999, ISO 1999, Feedback 1999, Strategic plan and objectives 1999, F. Greenslade departure 1999, Board meeting prep 1999-2001, President announcement 1999, President's fund 1999, Colleague organizations 1999 (Box 92)
  - Contraceptive timeline 2000, K. Rogo objectives 2000, Internal newsletter 2000, Staff meeting 2000, Bylaws 2000, China white paper 2000, L. Maguire correspondence 2000, President's message to Board 00, Objectives 2000, One pager on Ipas work 2000, Legislation 2000, Matrix guidelines 00, Speech to LAC region 2000, Key initiatives 2000-2001, Euro-donors 2000-2001, Staff 2000-2001, Results framework 2000-2001, Support staff task force 2000-2002, HR 2000-2003, World Health Organization meeting 2000, Eurodonors 2001, Senior staff 2001, Franchise information 2001, Planning and evaluation 2001, Interviewing 2001, Cluster meetings 2001-2002, Internal procedures 2001-2002, R and E 2001-2002, Staff bios 2001-2002, L. Maguire correspondence 2001, Global Health Council 2001, Gag Rule 2001, September 11 2001, L. Maguire correspondence 2002, Adolescents 2002, Dakar PAC 2002, Paris trip 2002, 63iii 2002, Guyana 2002, Gag Rule 2002, Internal reports 2002, Personnel policy 2002, Priorities 2002, Structure 2002, ET retreats 2002-2003, ET meetings 2002-2004, Asia 2003, Henry David party 2003, Comms Advisory Group 2003, Board 2003, Development 03, HIV working group 2003, Talks 2004 (Box 93)